[{"answer": "Never you mind.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "Do you still think he's sexy?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, there's not a day goes by when I don't get up and say thank you to somebody.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "What do you think -- when you sit here in this room, what do you think?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "Most of the time.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "How much time do you spend here?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "And do you like it here?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "I suppose I miss the British cynicism and the humor.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "What do you miss, though, about back home?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "That's a very dangerous question.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Would you plead guilty to that?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "No, no, absolutely impossible.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "I mean can you remember the names of every woman that you've taken to bed?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Quite honest --", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "But you feel guilty that you can't remember?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "I'm married to her.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "What's sort the perfect Rod Stewart woman?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "So a leggy blond, basically.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "I did say that, didn't I?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "People ask me that and all I can put it down to is my infatuation with Marilyn Monroe when I was younger and you know maybe Brigitte Bardot, because when I was a kid, you know, preteens and going into teens, they were the two blonde idols.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "Why blondes?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "That potential age gap?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "You don't look massively encumbered by stresses of life, I must say.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "Do I look a worried man?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "I think we were more or less resigned to the fact that if it doesn't work we've got one wonderful son with Alastair and you know I've been very fortunate -- I mean eight children now so I wouldn't have complained.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "How hard when you thought perhaps, you know, it may never work?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "I was at the Kremlin doing a show in Russia, Moscow, and Penny phoned me up and says, we've done it, we've done it, we've done it, and we both just burst into tears.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Where were you when you heard the good news?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "You should ask me kids that maybe.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Are you a good dad, do you think?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "The fine line between spoiling a child and depriving has always been difficult for me because I've come from a working class background and now you know wonderful wealth so it's hard for me not to spoil them and it's difficult -- I find it very difficult.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "What have you learned that perhaps you didn't know when you were younger?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "No, I don't think so.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Do you spoil them, do you think?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Well, it's a double-edged sword.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "How do you deal about price of fame for your kids?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "TEWART: Happy ending.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "I think that's had a happy ending, hasn't it?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "Yes, I feel guilty about everything.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Do you feel guilty about it?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "We're not weirdoes.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "What do you call it?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Well it's been in magazines.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "No one has ever seen it, have they?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Seriously?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "No, no, no, it's really private.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "So we can't see it then?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "It's the length of this house.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "The size of this room?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "It's not a question of trains.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "How many trains do you have?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "People still watching this?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Singing?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "I didn't get any reaction at all.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Did you love that instant chemistry with an audience, the reaction that you got?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Oh, man, probably when I saw Mick and the Stones over at Eel Pie Island.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "What was the moment when you thought, I want to be a rock star?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "So you're watching Mick Jagger who the hot rock star.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "A sports car.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "And what did you hope being a rock star would bring you?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "That transformation possess, was there a point when you thought, I've got to do this on my own?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Where would all this stuff go?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "No, we'd put it in the elevator and sent it down to the lobby.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "Out the window?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "There was The Who.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Was there anyone that matched you and Ronnie?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "But when that happened, when it just exploded, what was that time like for you because that was stratospherically, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "No, that's bullocks.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "I have gone into the pub for a couple of hours, get a bit of Dutch courage.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Would you do it?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "I mean could you imagine doing a duet with her singing?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "I think it's beautiful.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "What do you think of her voice technically?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Another dangerous question.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "How did you deal with the first negativity that came your way?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Because I mean look at me.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Why did they go after you, do you think?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "No, we talked about that earlier.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "I supposed the obvious question, do you think you're sexy?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "What's the Rod Stewart magic with women?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "It's an inner thing, it's a look in the eye.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "What to you is sexy?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "Or were you?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "Of course, I do.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Do you regret that?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "So you --", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "My dad told me.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "I was going to say, I mean, were you just too young?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "TEWART: I don't think you put an age on it.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "I mean if you had your time again what age would you get married, do you think?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Oh yes, it certainly was, yes, very hurtful.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Wasn't it?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "She was too young.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Why do you think it didn't work out, when you look back on it?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Me sister Mary told me brother.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "I think because my sister Mary understands that women do a lot of growing between 21 and 30, you know, which Rachel probably has.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Why did she think that?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah, bloody hell did it.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Did it break your heart, do you think?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "It was a good six months of, you know, laying upstairs looking at the ceiling in bed, couldn't get out of bed, depression, didn't drink for six month.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Did you feel, wow, this is what it feels like?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Didn't drink for six months.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "ORGAN: Did you not?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "Well, there's no way of getting over it.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "How did you get over it?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Probably, you know, I'm a better listener now than I've ever been before.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "But what were the lessons you had to learn from that not working, that second marriage?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "Yeah, I used to say it, but now I'm all over it like a dirty rag, Penny, every morning, love you darling, I love you pussycat.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Well, it was at the Dorchester Hotel.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "But the first moment you saw her, what did you think?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "Yeah, without a doubt.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "Are you as happy now as you've ever been?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "She's naughty.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "But what was it about her that gave you contentment, do you think?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "Beyond a doubt.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "Do you think she's the one?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "Didn't even think it could be cancer.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "When you got that call, what were you thinking?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "Yeah, yeah.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "But did you get a sense then of your own mortality for the first time?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "Yeah, yeah, I didn't -- no, I didn't when I went into the surgery.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "Did you think to yourself, I could die here?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "I was frightened, really scared, and all sorts of thoughts were going through my mind, you know, of becoming a landscape gardener.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 692, "question": "What was going through your mind, seriously?", "qSentId": 691}, {"answer": "Yes, exactly six months after the operation, five or six month.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "Was there a moment when -- like a Eureka moment when you knew you were back?", "qSentId": 700}, {"answer": "Well, I could do an hour of singing.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "What was the moment?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "It can include football, but for this audience --", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 715, "question": "Outside of football?", "qSentId": 714}, {"answer": "Well, you know, the business has been very kind to me.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "Or are you content now to keep rocking at the level that you are?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "Yeah, it is.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 749, "question": "It's extraordinary that you've had this career resurgence on great American songs?", "qSentId": 748}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 752, "question": "When you had the idea, quite a gamble for you to do that?", "qSentId": 751}, {"answer": "First I had the idea in the '80s.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 754, "question": "Were there people telling you don't do this?", "qSentId": 753}, {"answer": "I'm supposed to do a Christmas album sometime.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 769, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 768}, {"answer": "Yeah, man.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 772, "question": "You can do a country album?", "qSentId": 771}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 781, "question": "Do you still get the same kick out of touring?", "qSentId": 780}, {"answer": "Well, Celtie beating Rangers is good.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 783, "question": "Is it still the one thing that is more exciting than anything else?", "qSentId": 782}, {"answer": "I don't suffer nerves like I used to.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 792, "question": "What is that feeling like?", "qSentId": 791}, {"answer": "You can see it, mate.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 800, "question": "How do you know when you've got them?", "qSentId": 799}, {"answer": "It's tremendous, yes.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 804, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 803}, {"answer": "Yeah, yeah, it is.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 806, "question": "Is that the greatest feeling?", "qSentId": 805}, {"answer": "No, no, it's not that good, mate.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 808, "question": "ORGAN: Is that better than sex?", "qSentId": 807}, {"answer": "I'm a celebrity, get me out of here.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 814, "question": "What would you like your epitaph to be?", "qSentId": 813}, {"answer": "Just as an honest guy who loved his football, just a simple man really who got extremely lucky, extremely lucky.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 817, "question": "Do you have a way you would like to be remembered then?", "qSentId": 816}, {"answer": "Well, you know, they saw me break through in the early '70s.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 819, "question": "If your parents could be sitting now watching this, what do you think they would have thought?", "qSentId": 818}, {"answer": "Yeah, they would, I'm sure.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 823, "question": "They would be proud of you as a man, do you think, the way you've evolved?", "qSentId": 822}, {"answer": "Yeah, not compared to some.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 836, "question": "You've lost lots of money?", "qSentId": 835}, {"answer": "Sort of.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 839, "question": "Do you know how much you're worth?", "qSentId": 838}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 855, "question": "Is there a moment when your pride would say to you, enough?", "qSentId": 854}, {"answer": "The Barnett (ph) going.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 858, "question": "What would be the worst thing for you?", "qSentId": 857}, {"answer": "I don't know how I would cope with that.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 860, "question": "Bald?", "qSentId": 859}, {"answer": "Go on.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 863, "question": "Do you know what it is?", "qSentId": 862}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 877, "question": "Would you say you're vain on that?", "qSentId": 876}, {"answer": "Well, it wasn't going to be that, but maybe it's something you want to tell me, Rod.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 889, "question": "Are you gay?", "qSentId": 888}, {"answer": "No, not today I'm not.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 891, "question": "No, no, it's actually whether you're still wearing women's underwear?", "qSentId": 890}, {"answer": "Just for one show.", "docId": "110330pmt", "aSentId": 898, "question": "For what period of time were you wearing women's underwear?", "qSentId": 897}]